PERFIL

Hello my name is Anaisa but I go by Isa for most people and I am 31 years young woman. I am now living in North Rhine-Westphalia but moving to Munich in December for the new year coming.

Most of my life I have been in the hospitality sector, but in my head I have always been amazed in how people work with computers since

I didn't own one for several years. This year I decided to start a new challenge and change my career path. So I invested first in a laptop (MacBook Air) and after some searching

I found SheCodes Workshops who are definitely the best out there for teaching absolute beginners.

I am a person who works very well with a team or by myself, fast learner, good organisation skills and great work ethic because I always

commit 100% in new professional challenges.

I very easily integrate to new situations and work environment's.

The several work sceneries I have had is what has helped me acquire all this qualities.

PROFESSIONAL QUALITIES

Organisation
Work ethic
Team spirit
Initiative
Dedication and Effort
Fast Learner
Attention to detail
Punctual

ANAISA PEDRO

Address: Einsteinstraße 4681675 Munich

Phone nr: +49 1638068364 Email: isa.pedro92@hotmail.com Portfolio: https://main--portfolio-anaisa-pedro.netlify.app/

GitHub: https://github.com/lsapedro

EDUCATION

SheCodes, 14/08/23 - 15/10/23

SheCodes Basics and SheCodes Basics Add-on,

SheCodes Plus and SheCodes Plus Add-on,

SheCodes Responsive and SheCodes Responsive Add-on,

SheCodes React and SheCodes React Add-on,

SheCodes Next.

Google Digital Academy(Skillshop) 08/23

Fundamentals of digital marketing

OnHair Academy, Algés, 12/2020-09/2021

Professional Barber Training Finishing with 17 Values.

SVQ - Scottish Vocational Qualifications 01/2014 - 10/2014

Modern Apprenticeship in Hospitality Supervision and Leadership Finishing with 80 credits e SCQF level 7

Escola Secundária de Silves- 2008 - 2011

Language and Humanities Course

Professional experience

Eis Cafe San Remo, Coesfeld NRW, Germany

Eiskellnerin_01/03/23 - 30/09/23

Worked full time in a family owned business in a Ice cream cafe and bistro only for the high season. This job was mainly for adaptation to moving in to Germany.

Xilb Barber and Lounge Bar, Silves, Portugal

Barber and Bartender 16/01/2022 - 30/09/2022

Started this job as a barber but soon after become also bartender after the barbershop working hours. Worked with a team of 2 other professionals in the barbershop and become person responsible for the closing of the bar.

Barbairos, Barbearia e Garrafeira, Alfragide, Portugal

Barber 06/09/2021-30/12/2021

Started with a part-time in this barbershop while I was finishing the course of barber in the Onhair Academy. Becoming a full timer in October. Worked with a team of 3 professionals who supported me in every way possible of the start of the career path of barbering. It was a short experience due to needing to move back to my hometown. But deepen my knowledge and technics in "hot towel" shaving and perfected the hair cuts with razor machines and scissors given attention to what the client wanted.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Management Communications Critical thinking Front-end development Wireframe Creation Project management tools Problem solving, VS Code, Git GitHub, Bootstrap Hosting, HTML + CSS, JavaScript, API, Node, React.is Responsive Development, Strong Communication

CERTIFICATIONS

Introduction to Coding - 19/08/23
Introduction to Web Development - 22/08/23
Web Development - 06/09/23
Advanced Web Development - 08/09/23
Responsive Web Development - 21/09/23
Advanced Responsive Web
Development - 25/09/23
React Development - 05/10/23
Advanced React Development - 16/10/23
Fundamental of Digital Marketing - 14/08/23

LANGUAGES

Portuguese- native Inglês- fluent Espanhol- competent Italian - basic German- basic

Dishoom, Edinburgh, Scotland

<u>Server_</u>06/19- 08/20 <u>Cocktail Bartender_</u>12/18 - 06/19

I've started my career with this restaurant chain as a bartender where I continued to develop my knowledge and execution of all the drinks specified for the restaurant. When an opportunity came up to progress to a server position I decided I should try and was the successful one. This positions are solely internal applications due to the high level of knowledge you are needed to have about all the products, ingredients and drinks. Working in Dishoom was a very fundamental enriching experience that I enjoyed a lot.

Old Poison Company, Edinburgh, Scotland

Sales Assistant/Bartender - 01/2018- 11/2019

Work alongside with a Gin based distillery as a sale assistant, in advertising the brand, in pop up cocktail bars/events. During this time I was helping in the preparation for the events and making of the drinks using the gin. (Selkie Gin)

The Refinery, Edinburgh Scotland

Cocktail Bartender Supervisor 10/2017 - 08/2018

Has cocktail bartender in The refinery I was quickly promoted to supervisor due to my organisation and previous team supervision experience. Has a supervisor I had the responsibility of ordering stock, checking the deliveries, supervise guide and teach the new member of staff, and cash up.

The Brunswick Pub, Brighton, England

Bar Supervisor 01/2018-09/2018

I was employed as part time bar staff then promoted to full time supervisor.

Duties Included: Training new staff members, overlooking trial shifts. Also cellar trained.

Radisson Blu Hotel, Edinburgh Scotland

<u>Supervisor of the Bar</u>: Itchycoo Kitchen and Bar 09/2016 - 11/2016 <u>Supervisor Breakfast Room -</u> The Restaurant 09/2015 - 09/16

<u>Shift-Leader: 10</u>/2013 - 09/2015

Room-Service attendant 03/2012 - 10/2013

<u>Server</u> 10/2011 - 03/2012

Finalist for Carlson Rezidor Supervisor/ Shift Leader Shining Star of the Year 2015, across Great Britain, finishing on top 4.